fafarazzi.com 2011-01-20

# About Fafarazzi.com - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We aggregate information on what pages users visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as site registration information). 

The information we collect is used to improve the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

* It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.  
* We transfer information about you if Eastland Media or Fafarazzi is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Eastland Media will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**COLLECTING INFORMATION, USAGE**

* When you register for Fafarazzi we ask for information such as your email address and date of birth. If you are signing up for a private league we ask for information such as your billing address and credit card information. Your credit card information is never stored by Fafarazzi.  
* Eastland Media uses collected information for the following general purposes: billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. 

**COOKIES**

* A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a site's server and stored on your computer's hard drive.  
* Fafarazzi does not require cookies for usage of the service. Cookies are used only voluntarily through the login page.  
* Fafarazzi will access your information when you "sign in" so we can provide you with customized content or remember the last page you visited in a Fafarazzi product or service.  
* We deliver advertisements relevant to your interests when you visit Fafarazzi, using a cookie that gathers anonymous information based on visits & activity to Fafarazzi.  
* If you would rather not receive customized advertising off of Fafarazzi, you can [opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of this service or disable cookies through your browser.  
* **If you want to control which cookies you accept:** You can order your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. Then you can decide whether to accept one or not.  
* **[Opting out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of a network** does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns. 

**DISCLOSURE**

* Eastland Media may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. 

**CHANGES TO POLICY**

* Eastland Media may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your Fafarazzi account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**QUESTIONS?**

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to info@fafarazzi.com or by mail at: Eastland Media, 29 Miller St. Somerville, MA 02143.
